Yuuji Itadori, by law I will
now exorcize you as a curse.
(dramatic orchestral music)
No, really, I'm feeling fine.
Besides, you and I are
both pretty beat up.
Shouldn't we see a doctor?
[Fushiguro] I can't tell
if this is Itadori speaking
or the cursed object.
Dammit, what do I do now?
[Satoru] What's the situation?
Huh, Satoru Gojou?
What are you doing here?
Hey.
I wasn't planning on showing up,
but you got kind
of roughed up, kid.
I'll show the second years.
Say cheese.
(laughs)
I got an earful
from the higher-ups
'cause this special-grade
cursed object's still missing.
Thought I'd do a little
sightseeing and stop by.
So, did you find it yet?
(Fushiguro sighs)
-Uh--
-Hmm?
Sorry, but I ate that thing.
Really?
-He did.
-I did.
Hmm?
Hmm.
(laughs)
Damn, it really did
combine with you.
That's hilarious.
Anything weird about your body?
Nah, it seems okay.
Can you swap
with Sukuna at will?
Sukuna?
[Satoru] Yeah,
the curse you ate?
Oh, mm-hmm, yeah,
I think I can do that.
Okay, give us 10 seconds.
Then change right
back into yourself.
Yeah, but..
Don't worry.
I'm way too strong for him.
Megumi, hold onto this for me.
So what is this?
Kikufuku from Kikusuian.
It's Sendai's specialty
and it's super good.
I recommend the
zunda and cream flavor.
[Fushiguro] This guy actually
went and bought souvenirs
while people were
out here dying?
It's no souvenir.
I'll be eating this on the
bullet train ride home.
(thunder crashes)
Look out!
-Kikufuku's just the best.
-(thunder crashes)
(intense music)
I think it's the
whipped cream inside
that really makes
the difference.
(Sukuna growls)
Since my student's watching,
I think I'll show off a little.
Yeah.
(fighters grunting)
Is he unbelievably fast?
No, that's not it.
(fighters grunting)
For crying out loud.
You jujutsu sorcerers are
always such a pain in the ass
in any era.
(building crashing)
(glass shatters)
Though time doesn't really
have much meaning for me.
Seven, eight, nine.
And that should do it.
[Sukuna] Dammit, again?
Why can't I seem to
take over this body?
Who the hell is
this Itadori punk?
[Itadori] Oh, how did it go?
How about that?
So you really can
control that guy?
He's kind of annoying
though to tell the truth
and I keep hearing his voice.
It's a miracle that's
all he's doing to you.
[Megumi] What'd you do to him?
[Satoru] I just knocked him out.
If he isn't possessed by
Sukuna when he wakes up,
then he might have
potential as a vessel.
Now I have a question for you.
What do you think
we should do with him?
Well, even if he is a vessel,
jujutsu regulations
demand Itadori be executed.
However, I don't
want him to die.
Personal?
I suppose.
So can you save him?
(Satoru chuckles)
A request from a
precious student?
Leave it to me.
But the end result
is still your execution.
Your recap doesn't match
with the current events.
Hey, sorry, I did my best.
You still have to die, but I
got your sentence suspended.
What's suspended mean?
You'll wait until
later to kill me?
Yep, I'll just explain
from the top.
This is the same kind of thing
as the cursed object you ate.
There are 20 of these in total.
We possess six of them.
[Itadori] 20?
Oh, each finger and toe?
No, Sukuna has four arms.
(finger exploding)
As you can see, we
can't destroy them.
The curse is that powerful
and the curse grows
stronger every day.
So our modern-day jujutsu
seals just aren't keeping up.
That's where you come in.
When you die, the curse
inside you will die as well.
You see, our elders are cowards.
They're demanding
we kill you right away.
But that would be a
waste, wouldn't you say?
-A waste?
-See,
there's no assurance
another vessel capable
of handling Sukuna
will ever be born again,
so here's what I
proposed to them.
Since they've already
decided to execute you,
why not wait until after
you've absorbed all
of Sukuna to do it?
And the higher-ups agreed.
So now, you have
two options before you.
You can die here and now or
gather all the parts of Sukuna,
absorb them and then die.
(Opening Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
(person knocking)
[Sasaki] Itadori.
Hi.
Hello, Sasaki.
How's Iguchi doing?
Well, the doctors say
there's nothing
seriously wrong with him,
but he still hasn't
regained consciousness
and this whole thing's my fault.
I asked him to come to
the school and that night...
(sobs)
I know you won't believe
it, but we got attacked.
By some weird scary monster.
And it captured both of us.
I do believe you
'cause I know that
wasn't a monster exactly.
It was a curse.
Huh?
That finger was a
special-grade cursed object.
It has the power to
draw other curses to it
and make them stronger.
So none of what happened
here was your fault.
It was mine for giving it
to you in the first place.
(soft piano music)
So I'm sorry, but
it'll be all right.
Someone who can fix
Iguchi will be here tomorrow.
Itadori?
Sorry, Sasaki, but I have
somewhere I have to be.
Ba-bye.
[Satoru] Who passed away?
[Itadori] My grandpa,
although he was more
like a father to me.
[Satoru] I see.
Sorry it had to happen
at a time like this.
So, have you decided
what you want to do?
[Itadori] Are
casualties like these
from curses pretty common?
This one was a rather
exceptional case,
but in terms of damage,
it happens all the time.
It's a good night when
someone dies a normal death
after encountering a curse.
Finding a body
that's torn to pieces
is actually one of
the better outcomes.
If you plan to hunt down Sukuna,
you're going to witness
some gruesome stuff
and I can't guarantee you
won't end up that way yourself.
So, I guess you can
choose which hell you want.
[Grandpa] You're a strong
kid, so try to help others.
[Itadori] If all the parts
of Sukuna were gone,
would it really help?
Would there be fewer people
getting harmed by curses?
Yes, of course.
So have you got that finger?
Looking at it again
here in broad daylight,
it's pretty disgusting.
(swallows)
Okay, that's the second one.
One tenth of the whole.
I wonder what's going to happen.
-(Itadori gagging)
-(Sukuna growling)
(Itadori chuckles)
Blech.
So gross.
I mean, so gross it's funny.
[Satoru] (chuckles) There.
It's not just a physical
tolerance that he has.
He can fight off Sukuna's
attempts to take over.
We haven't seen someone
with talent like this
-in 1,000 years.
-What's wrong?
-(rock music)
-Oh, nothing at all.
I take it this means
you've made up your mind.
Chosen your fate?
Not at all.
I still don't understand
why I have to be executed,
but I know I can't
just do nothing.
Grandpa, that last
request of yours
is going to be
a pain in the ass.
I'll eat every part of Sukuna.
After that, I don't care.
As far as how I'm gonna
die, I've already decided.
My guy, I love
finding guys like you.
A fun time in hell awaits.
Make sure you're packed
by the end of the day.
Am I going somewhere?
Tokyo.
Fushiguro!
Looking good, brother.
You think this is looking good?
Anyway, here's the deal.
You're going to the school
for jujutsu sorcerers
that I attend.
Huh?
Tokyo Metropolitan Jujutsu
Technical High School.
By the way, you'll be one
of only three first years there.
Only three?
(bird squawking)
Okay, I'm heading out.
Goodbye, Grandpa.
This is really deep
in the mountains.
Are we still even in Tokyo?
[Satoru] This is what the
outskirts of Tokyo looks like.
[Itadori] Where's Fushiguro?
[Satoru] He's being
treated by a sorcerer
and at the moment,
he's fast asleep.
Tokyo Metropolitan Jujutsu
Technical High School.
It's one of only two
jujutsu educational facilities.
As a sort of cover,
it's known as a
private religious school.
Many jujutsu sorcerers
continue to use it as a base
after graduation,
so it's a pillar
of the jujutsu community,
not just in education,
but for support and
mediation in missions.
Anyway, you're about
to have an interview
with the Principal.
[Itadori] The Principal?
Screw this up
and he could turn you down
for admission just like that.
Huh?
And what happens then,
immediate execution?
What's this?
So you're not the boss?
Any hierarchy other
than strength is worthless.
(Itadori yells)
I'm sorry about that.
Sometimes he just does that.
What an amusing
body you have now.
I do owe you a big favor though.
Once I make this
punk's body my own,
you'll be the first one I kill.
It's my honor to be
targeted by Sukuna himself.
This guy is really that famous?
Ryoumen Sukuna is
an imaginary fierce god
with four arms and two faces.
But he once existed as
an actual human being,
although it was over
a thousand years ago.
In the golden age of jujutsu,
sorcerers gathered
all their might
to challenge him and failed.
Crowned with
the title of Sukuna,
we couldn't even
destroy his grave wax
as he traversed the ages
after death as a cursed object.
Without a doubt, he
is the king of curses.
[Itadori] Who's
stronger, him or you?
[Satoru] Well, if Sukuna
regained all his power,
he might cause
me a little trouble.
But would you lose?
I would win.
You're late, Satoru.
Eight minutes late.
As usual, not quite
enough to chastise you for.
I told you, fix that habit.
That old dude's
making cute things?
If it's not enough
to chastise me for,
then don't chastise.
Besides, you're just sitting
around making dolls anyway,
so what's eight minutes?
Principal Masamichi Yaga.
This is the boy?
Yuuji Itadori.
I'm into girls like
Jennifer Lawrence.
This is an honor.
[Principal] What
are you here for?
An interview?
But why Jujutsu Tech?
To learn jujutsu?
I mean beyond that.
What do you hope to find
once you've studied curses
and learned the art
of exorcizing them?
Well, I suppose,
I'm going to collect all
the fingers of Sukuna.
Can't just leave
them all out there.
-Why not?
-Hmm?
People you'll never
know die every day
due to crime,
accidents, and diseases.
It's just the natural
course of life.
Here he goes again.
But you're telling me
you can't overlook it
when that death is
caused by a curse?
It was someone's
dying request of me.
And I don't care
about the details.
I just want to save who I can.
Hmm, dying wish?
You're saying
you'll fight curses
just because someone
else told you to do that?
Insufficient.
(Itadori gasps)
(creature growls)
That's not a doll.
It's alive.
In a way.
They're corpses.
Dolls that I've
infused with my curse.
(Itadori gasps)
(Itadori grunts)
[Itadori] That's
one hell of a doll.
A person's true nature
reveals itself during a crisis.
I'll keep attacking you until
I get an acceptable answer.
Look, man, it wasn't
just someone else.
It was my grandfather's
dying request.
(grunts)
Where is it?
Family's still just
someone else.
(doll squeaking)
[Itadori] All
right, it's a doll,
so it doesn't get
hurt or scared.
A jujutsu sorcerer
constantly faces death
and not just their own death.
Sometimes you must
ignore the victims
and rend the flesh from those
who the curse has murdered.
It's an unpleasant job.
You have to be highly motivated
and perhaps a little
crazy to handle it.
You'd do this because
someone else told you to?
Don't make me laugh.
It would be more believable
if you said you were doing it
to postpone your execution.
Oh, screw you.
-I--
-And tell me this.
Are you going to blame
your poor grandfather
when you get
killed by a curse too?
Damn, old man.
You say some
pretty harsh things.
Teaching is making
people realize truths.
That's right, I guess.
(grunts)
[Principal] It's not easy
to imagine how you'll
feel on the verge of death.
However, I can say
one thing for certain.
At the rate you're going,
you might end up cursing
your beloved grandfather
for his dying wish.
Jujutsu sorcerers
never die without regret,
so I'll ask you just once more.
Why have you come
here to Jujutsu Tech?
(melancholy music)
As a kid, I was always
better than most
in sports and in fights,
but never once did I think
this is something only I can do.
Never.
(grunts)
Consuming Sukuna is
something only I can do.
So even if I could
escape my death sentence
and run away from
this responsibility,
then someday I'd be eating food,
taking a bath, or reading manga
and the moment
I stopped to think,
I'd go, "Oh, I bet
that right now
"somewhere out there, someone
is dying because of Sukuna."
But that doesn't concern me.
It's certainly not my fault.
You expect me
to tell myself that?
-(rock music)
-Well, I refuse to do that.
I don't know how I'll
feel when I'm dying,
but I won't regret
the way I lived.
Satoru, show him
to his dorm room.
Be sure to explain the security
arrangements to him as well.
You're admitted.
Welcome to Jujutsu Tech.
(Itadori yells)
Sorry, I forgot to
release the curse.
[Itadori] Whoa!
This place is huge.
All the second and third
years are out at the moment,
but you'll meet
them all soon enough.
There aren't many of them.
You know, there's no real
reason for you to go fight at all.
Fushiguro and I could
retrieve Sukuna's fingers
while you just stay
here and chill out.
Yeah, nice try, guy.
I said I'd do it and I will.
Hey, dude.
Though I gotta say,
hanging out until Fushiguro
comes back all beat up
just to bring me a finger,
that would be funny.
Yeah, but you wouldn't
have refused to fight.
I already knew that.
Huh, that was a test?
If the fingers were
that easy to find,
don't you think we'd have
collected them all already?
Some have a presence
that's overwhelming.
Some keep very quiet
and some have already been
absorbed by a curse spirit.
These are the challenges
we've dealt with
when it comes to
searching for them.
But at last we have you.
The Sukuna within you
will try to regain his power
and that will lead
us to the fingers.
You're both vessel and
locator, our very own radar.
So you see, we won't
get very far without you.
Are you sure he's going
to be that cooperative?
Oh, I think we can come to
a win-win agreement there.
[Fushiguro] You're next door.
Hey, Fushiguro.
Wow, you look all better now.
There's lots of other
empty rooms, you know?
Sure, but isn't it better
to have some company?
I thought it'd be good.
Classes and missions are enough.
This is not welcome.
Whoa, it's so organized in here.
Back off.
I just told you,
you're not welcome.
Ha, friends already.
And together we're
heading out tomorrow.
We're going to go pick up
the third and final first-year.
(train horn)
[PA] The train bound
for Tokyo is now arriving.
Please stand behind
the yellow line.
(Nobara grunts)
Four hours and I'm
still only in Morioka,
but at least I can finally kiss
that damn countryside goodbye.
And I'll be in Tokyo
by this afternoon.
What should I do
if I get scouted?
Like by Stardust?
(Closing Theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
(ominous music)